Alright, now let me give you an overview
Tudo bem, agora, deixe-me dar uma viso geral de
of how I have structured this course real quick. In the next section,
como estruturei esse curso rapidamente. Na prxima seo, voc aprender os
you're going to learn the fundamentals of unit testing. In this section,
fundamentos do teste de unidade. Nesta seo, veremos as
we'll be looking at characteristics of good and trustworthy unit
caractersticas dos testes unitrios bons e confiveis, veremos
tests, we'll be looking at naming and organizing tests,
os testes de nomeao e organizao, a redao
writing some basic unit tests, as well as creating parameterized
de alguns testes unitrios bsicos e a criao
tests. Once you master the fundamentals, then
de testes parametrizados. Depois de dominar os fundamentos, estaremos analisando
we'll be looking at the core unit testing techniques. In this section,
as principais tcnicas de teste de unidade. Nesta seo, em cada
in each lecture, I'm going to show you an example of a function to test.
palestra, mostrarei um exemplo de uma funo para testar.
Each function shows you a scenario that you see in a lot of real world applications.
Cada funo mostra um cenrio que voc v em muitos aplicativos do mundo real.
The following section is all about exercises.
A seo a seguir  sobre exerccios.
So in that section, I will give you three unit testing exercises,
Ento, nessa seo, darei trs exerccios de teste de unidade,
and you will have a chance to put what you learned in the first two sections
e voc ter a chance de colocar o que aprendeu
in practice. For each exercise, you can see my solution as well.
nas duas primeiras sees na prtica. Para cada exerccio, voc pode ver minha soluo tambm.
Now up to this point all our unit tests are for
Agora, at este ponto, todos os nossos testes de unidade
simple classes that don't have any external dependencies.
so para classes simples que no possuem dependncias externas.
But in the real world our code often talks to a database, a web
Mas no mundo real, nosso cdigo geralmente fala com um banco de dados, um
service and so on. So section five is all about dealing with
servio da Web e assim por diante. Ento, a seo cinco trata de
these external dependencies. In this section, you will learn about
lidar com essas dependncias externas. Nesta seo, voc aprender
concepts such as dependency injection, and mocking.
sobre conceitos como injeo de dependncia e simulao.
The following section, again, is all about exercises. So,
A seo a seguir, novamente,  sobre exerccios. Ento, vamos dar uma olhada
we'll look at three examples of code that touches an external resource.
em trs exemplos de cdigo que tocam em um recurso externo.
And finally, the last two sections include more
E finalmente, as duas ltimas sees incluem
challenges and exercises. I will show you a snippet of source code,
mais desafios e exerccios. Vou mostrar-lhe um trecho de cdigo-fonte,
taken from a real project, and your job is to write all the
retirado de um projeto real, e seu trabalho  escrever todos os
necessary unit tests for that code. And of course, we're going to see
testes de unidade necessrios para esse cdigo. E, claro, vamos ver
my solution as well.
a minha soluo tambm.